[
	{"question": "What is Glalie's Hidden Ability?","answers":["Moody"]},
	{"question": "What is Shuckle's Hidden Ability?","answers":["Contrary"]},
	{"question": "What is Ash's name in the Japanese anime?","answers":["Satoshi"]},
	{"question": "What is Gary's name in the Japanese anime?","answers":["Shigeru"]},
	{"question": "Which Pokémon is found at Sky Pillar?","answers":["Rayquaza"]},
	{"question": "In Ruby/Sapphire/Emerald you receieve an egg in Lavaridge town. Which Pokémon hatches from the egg?","answers":["Wynaut"]},
	{"question": "Zorua/Zorark's illusion ability let's the take the name and appearance of which Pokémon in your party?","answers":["6th","last","6","sixth"]},
	{"question": "This Pokémon is said to live in a world on the reverse side of ours, where common knowledge is distorted and strange. Who's that Pokémon?","answers":["Giratina"]},
	{"question": "What is Giratina's Hidden Ability?","answers":["Telepathy"]},
	{"question": "What is Honchkrow's Hidden Ability?","answers":["Moxie"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokémon type to not yet have a Gym that specializes in it?","answers":["Dark"]},
	{"question": "What two types are the only types that are both not very effective against each other?","answers":["fighting-bug","Bug and Fighting","fighting and bug","bug/fighting","fighting/bug","bug fighting","fighting bug","bug & fighting","fighting & bug","bug-fighting"]},
	{"question": "Name a bug Pokémon that can learn Fly?","answers":["Volcarona","Genesect"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon type is the most common among legendary/mythical Pokémon?","answers":["Psychic"]},
	{"question": "Mow Rotom's typing was originally Electric and what?","answers":["Ghost"]},
	{"question": "Who is the only Flying type with Levitate?","answers":["rotom-fan","Fan Rotom","rotom fan","fan-rotom"]},
	{"question": "Who is the champion of the Hoenn region in Ruby/Sapphire?","answers":["Steven"]},
	{"question": "What is Steven's signature Pokémon as champion of Ruby/Sapphire?","answers":["Metagross"]},
	{"question": "Where do you find Groudon/Kyogre?","answers":["Cave of Origin","origin cave"]},
	{"question": "Of the following Pokémon, which one is NOT found in trophy garden in Diamond/Pearl/Platinum: Ditto, Chansey, Pikachu?","answers":["Pikachu"]},
	{"question": "Who is the Elite Four member who makes an appearance in both Kanto's and Johto's Pokémon league as Elite Four only?","answers":["Bruno"]},
	{"question": "What HM does Ash teach his Greninja in the anime?","answers":["1","HM1","hm 1","Cut"]},
	{"question": "Who won the Sun/Moon Nuzlocke challenge?","answers":["gearhead7","Grant","Gearhead"]},
	{"question": "How many semi-pseudo Legendary Pokémon are there?","answers":["seven","7"]},
	{"question": "What is a pseudo Legendary Pokémon that is NOT a dragon type?","answers":["Tyranitar","Metagross or Tyranitar","Metagross"]},
	{"question": "It disguises itself as a tree to avoid attack. It hates water, so it will disappear if it starts raining. Who's that Pokémon?","answers":["Sudowoodo"]},
	{"question": "It can freely change its body's color. The zigzag pattern on its belly doesn't change, however. Who's that Pokémon?","answers":["Kecleon"]},
	{"question": "A ball that is more effective as more turns are taken in battle. What kind of Pokéball is it?","answers":["Timer","Timer ball"]},
	{"question": "What item do you need to evolve a Seadra?","answers":["Dragonscale","Dragon Scale"]},
	{"question": "A cozy ball that makes Pokémon more friendly. What Pokéball is this?","answers":["Luxury","Luxury ball"]},
	{"question": "Norman is the Gym Leader of which city?","answers":["Petalburg"]},
	{"question": "What town is Ash from?","answers":["Pallet Town"]},
	{"question": "What is the region in Pokémon Colosseum called?","answers":["Orre"]},
	{"question": "What is the name of Team Snagem's leader?","answers":["Gonzap"]},
	{"question": "Shadow Lugia in Pokémon XD: Gale of Darkness is also known as...?","answers":["XD001"]},
	{"question": "How do you evolve Eevee into Umbreon in Pokémon XD: Gale of Darkness?","answers":["Moon Dust"]},
	{"question": "In Fire Red/Leaf Green, you encountered a legendary dog (Suicune, Raikou, Entei) based on your ________?","answers":["starter","Starter Pokémon","starter pokemon"]},
	{"question": "In Gold/Silver/Crystal/Heart Gold/Soul Silver, Team Rocket stole an item and hid it in the Cerulean City Gym. What is the name of this item?","answers":["Machine Part"]},
	{"question": "What is the name of a gym leader who becomes an Elite Four member in the next generation?","answers":["Iris","Koga or Iris","Koga"]},
	{"question": "In Generation 1, this move can be countered for infinite damage on the turn it breaks a Substitute. What is this move?","answers":["Guillotine"]},
	{"question": "Which Pokémon excluding Smeargle, can learn the most one-hit KO moves?","answers":["Lapras"]},
	{"question": "Which starter type always comes first in the Pokédex?","answers":["Grass"]},
	{"question": "What is the only move to start with a Y?","answers":["Yawn"]},
	{"question": "What ability is a copy of Huge Power?","answers":["Pure Power"]},
	{"question": "What ability is a copy of Clear Body?","answers":["White Smoke"]},
	{"question": "What ability is a copy of Rough Skin?","answers":["Iron Barbs"]},
	{"question": "What ability is a copy of Shell Armor?","answers":["Battle armour","Battle Armor"]},
	{"question": "What ability is a copy of Emergency Exit?","answers":["Wimp Out"]},
	{"question": "What ability allows the successful use of Sleep Talk without being asleep?","answers":["Comatose"]},
	{"question": "What is the priority of Fake Out?","answers":["3","+3","Three"]},
	{"question": "What is the priority of Extreme Speed?","answers":["2","+2","Two"]},
	{"question": "What is the priority of Protect?","answers":["4","+4","Four"]},
	{"question": "What pokémon has the ability Flower Gift?","answers":["Sunshine Cherrim","Cherrim"]},
	{"question": "What pokémon has the ability Fur Coat?","answers":["alola persian","Furfrou","Persian Alola"]},
	{"question": "What is the most common ability?","answers":["Levitate"]},
	{"question": "What is the most common type?","answers":["Water"]},
	{"question": "What was the only Dragon type move in Generation 1?","answers":["Dragon Rage"]},
	{"question": "Who was the only Dragon type Pokémon introduced in Generation 2?","answers":["Kingdra"]},
	{"question": "What must Sneasel be holding to evolve?","answers":["Razor Claw"]},
	{"question": "What move must Piloswine know to evolve?","answers":["Ancient Power"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon evolves at the highest level?","answers":["Zweilous"]},
	{"question": "What must Gligar be holding to evolve?","answers":["Razor Fang"]},
	{"question": "How many pokémon were introduced in Generation 1?","answers":["one hundred and fifty one","151"]},
	{"question": "Who is the only Pokémon to have a Pokédex number of #000?","answers":["MissingNo.","Victini"]},
	{"question": "Who is the only Pokémon besides Ditto that learns Transform?","answers":["Mew"]},
	{"question": "How many status conditions are there?","answers":["six","6"]},
	{"question": "How many weather conditions are there?","answers":["seven","7"]},
	{"question": "How many One Hit KO moves are there?","answers":["Four","4"]},
	{"question": "Who is the only Generation 5 Mega Pokémon?","answers":["Audino"]},
	{"question": "What is the only ability that has 3 copies of it, but with different names?","answers":["Turboblaze","Mold Breaker","Teravolt"]},
	{"question": "Name a special attack priority move?","answers":["Water Shuriken","Vacuum Wave"]},
	{"question": "What is the only priority multi-hit attack?","answers":["Water Shuriken"]},
	{"question": "What is the only type in Generation 1 besides Normal that is not super-effective against anything?","answers":["Dragon"]},
	{"question": "What berry reduces damage from Ice type attacks?","answers":["Yache","Yache Berry"]},
	{"question": "What berry reduces damage from Rock type attacks?","answers":["Charti","Charti Berry"]},
	{"question": "What berry reduces damage from Ground type attacks?","answers":["Shuca","Shuca Berry"]},
	{"question": "What does a Custap berry increase?","answers":["Priority"]},
	{"question": "What does a Ganlon berry increase?","answers":["Def","Defense"]},
	{"question": "What does a Wide Lens boost?","answers":["Accuracy"]},
	{"question": "What is the strongest Tier?","answers":["AG","Anything Goes"]},
	{"question": "What move must Bonsly know to evolve?","answers":["Mimic"]},
	{"question": "What egg group do all babies belong to?","answers":["Undiscovered"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Generation without a Rock type Gym(or Island Kahuna)?","answers":["Five","5","V"]},
	{"question": "What type has the fewest special attacking moves?","answers":["Rock"]},
	{"question": "Who is the Elite Four Champion in Generation 2?","answers":["Lance"]},
	{"question": "Who uses the infamous catch phrase 'Smell ya later'?","answers":["Blue"]},
	{"question": "Where can Red be battled in Generation 2?","answers":["Mt Silver","Mt. Silver"]},
	{"question": "Who is the Elite Four Champion in Generation 1?","answers":["Blue"]},
	{"question": "How many different types of Evolutionary Stones are there?","answers":["Nine","9"]},
	{"question": "The Unova Region is based off of what real life city?","answers":["NYC","New York City","New York"]},
	{"question": "The Kalos Region is based off of what real life city?","answers":["Paris"]},
	{"question": "The Alola Region is based off of what real life location?","answers":["Hawaii","Hawaiian Islands"]},
	{"question": "How many different pokémon types are there?","answers":["Eighteen","18"]},
	{"question": "How many types have been introduced since Generation 1?","answers":["Three","3"]},
	{"question": "Who has the highest base attack stat?","answers":["Mega Mewtwo X","Mewtwo X"]},
	{"question": "Who has the highest base HP stat?","answers":["Blissey"]},
	{"question": "Who has the highest base special attack stat?","answers":["Mega Mewtwo Y","Mewtwo Y"]},
	{"question": "Who has the highest base special defense stat?","answers":["Shuckle"]},
	{"question": "Who has the highest base defense stat?","answers":["Shuckle"]},
	{"question": "Who is tied with Mega Mewtwo X & Y with the highest base stat total?","answers":["Mega Rayquaza"]},
	{"question": "Who has the highest base speed stat?","answers":["Deoxys S","Deoxys Speed"]},
	{"question": "Who is the antagonistic team in Generation 6?","answers":["Flare","Team Flare"]},
	{"question": "Who is the antagonistic team in Generation 5?","answers":["Plasma","Team Plasma"]},
	{"question": "Who is the 'God' pokémon?","answers":["Arceus"]},
	{"question": "Name a starter with a dual type?","answers":["Bulbasaur","Rowlet"]},
	{"question": "What starter evolution line has more than 2 types, excluding megas?","answers":["Rowlet","Dartrix","Decidueye"]},
	{"question": "Who is the first pokémon in the National Dex?","answers":["Bulbasaur"]},
	{"question": "What Generation was Marill introduced in?","answers":["2","Two","II"]},
	{"question": "What move must Yanma know to evolve?","answers":["Ancient Power"]},
	{"question": "What move must Lickitung know to evolve?","answers":["Rollout"]},
	{"question": "As Rain is to water, Sandstorm is to ______?","answers":["Rock"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon is the unofficial mother to Cubone and Marowak?","answers":["Kangaskhan"]},
	{"question": "Who is the only legendary pokémon that can be either gender?","answers":["Heatran"]},
	{"question": "What level does Cosmoem evolve?","answers":["53","fiftythree","fifty-three"]},
	{"question": "What is the largest egg group?","answers":["Field","Field Egg Group"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon game first introduced a playable female character?","answers":["Crystal","Pokemon Crystal"]},
	{"question": "Who is the leader of Team Rocket?","answers":["Giovanni"]},
	{"question": "What is the signature move of Volcanion?","answers":["Steam Eruption"]},
	{"question": "What is the only move Smeargle cannot use, but can copy?","answers":["Hyperspace Fury"]},
	{"question": "What is the only move Smeargle cannot copy?","answers":["Chatter","Struggle"]},
	{"question": "What is the signature move of Arceus?","answers":["Judgment"]},
	{"question": "What is the signature move of Genesect?","answers":["Techno Blast"]},
	{"question": "What does OU stand for?","answers":["Overused","Over Used"]},
	{"question": "Smogon is German for what pokémon?","answers":["Koffing"]},
	{"question": "How many Pokémon are there in the national dex?","answers":["802","eight hundred and two"]},
	{"question": "Pseudo-Legendary Pokémon require a base stat total of what?","answers":["600","six hundred"]},
	{"question": "How many Pseudo-Legendary Pokémon are there?","answers":["8","Eight"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon is fighting with Nidorino in the opening for Pokémon Blue and Red?","answers":["Gengar"]},
	{"question": "How do you evolve Clefairy?","answers":["Moon Stone","Moon stone"]},
	{"question": "What is the max happiness (friendship)?","answers":["255"]},
	{"question": "What was the first game to include happiness (friendship) for Pokémon?","answers":["Pokemon Yellow","Yellow"]},
	{"question": "Happiness (friendship) is mainly needed to evolve what type of Pokémon?","answers":["Baby Pokemon","Baby"]},
	{"question": "Happiny must be holding what to evolve?","answers":["Oval Stone"]},
	{"question": "The grand prize for winning the lottery in Pokémon is what?","answers":["Master Ball","Masterball"]},
	{"question": "Safari Balls have the same catch rate as which other ball?","answers":["Great Ball","Greatball"]},
	{"question": "What does Pokémon stand for?","answers":["Pocket Monster"]},
	{"question": "How many forms does Furfrou have?","answers":["10","Ten"]},
	{"question": "How many forms does Vivillon have?","answers":["20","twenty"]},
	{"question": "What special move does Rock Star Pikachu know?","answers":["Meteor Mash"]},
	{"question": "What is the only two type attack move?","answers":["Flying Press"]},
	{"question": "Abilities were introduced in what generation?","answers":["3","Three"]},
	{"question": "The Special/Physical split happened in what generation?","answers":["4","Four"]},
	{"question": "Mew, Celebi, Jirachi, Arceus, Keldeo, and Diancie are all examples of what kind of pokémon?","answers":["Mythical pokemon","Mythical"]},
	{"question": "What is Heracross' Hidden Ability?","answers":["Moxie"]},
	{"question": "What is Exploud's Hidden Ability?","answers":["Scrappy"]},
	{"question": "What is the Hidden Ability of Durant?","answers":["Traunt"]},
	{"question": "What item increases the amount of HP returned from HP-draining moves?","answers":["Big Root"]},
	{"question": "Which generation did not introduce any new fossils?","answers":["2 or 7","2","Two","7","Seven"]},
	{"question": "How many weaknesses does Bug/Steel have?","answers":["1","one"]},
	{"question": "How many immunities does Normal/Ghost have?","answers":["3","three"]},
	{"question": "How many weaknesses does Grass/Ice have?","answers":["7","Seven"]},
	{"question": "What type is the rarest type?","answers":["Ice"]},
	{"question": "How many resistances does Steel have?","answers":["10","Ten"]},
	{"question": "What is the rarest mono typing?","answers":["Flying"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon has the most type immunities?","answers":["Shedinja"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokémon to have a lower base stat total than its pre-evolved form?","answers":["Shedinja"]},
	{"question": "What Generation introduced the most new Pokémon?","answers":["5","Five","V"]},
	{"question": "What is the lowest level any Pokémon naturally evolves at?","answers":["7","Seven"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon can be bought for 9999 coins in Pokémon Red?","answers":["Porygon"]},
	{"question": "How many forms does Rotom have, excluding Pokédex Rotom?","answers":["7","seven"]},
	{"question": "Dread, Earth, Pixie, Insect and Mind are all examples of what?","answers":["Plates","Plate"]},
	{"question": "How many evolutions does Eevee have?","answers":["8","Eight"]},
	{"question": "Cities in the Kanto Region take their name from what?","answers":["Colors","Colours","color","Colour"]},
	{"question": "Rayquaza must know what move in order to Mega evolve?","answers":["Dragon Ascent"]},
	{"question": "What level does Wartortle evolve at?","answers":["36"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokémon that recieved both a pre-evolution and evolution in the same generation?","answers":["Roselia"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon has the lowest base stat total?","answers":["Sunkern"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon is known as The Being of Knowledge?","answers":["Uxie"]},
	{"question": "What year was the first Pokémon game released?","answers":["1996"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon has the most forms?","answers":["Unown"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon has over a billion different sprites/models?","answers":["Spinda"]},
	{"question": "What is the only move an Unown can learn?","answers":["Hidden Power"]},
	{"question": "Hidden Power's type is based off of a Pokémon's what?","answers":["IV","IVS"]},
	{"question": "What does IV stand for?","answers":["Individual Values","Individual Value"]},
	{"question": "What does EV stand for?","answers":["Effort Values","Effort value"]},
	{"question": "What is the max number of EVs a Pokémon can have?","answers":["510"]},
	{"question": "What is the max IV a Pokémon can have in a stat?","answers":["31"]},
	{"question": "What is the only way Shaymin-Sky can revert back into Shaymin during a battle?","answers":["Being frozen","Frozen","Freeze"]},
	{"question": "What item transforms Shaymin into Shaymin-Sky?","answers":["Gracidea Flower","Gracidea"]},
	{"question": "What item transforms the Forces of Nature trio into their Therian Forme?","answers":["Reveal Glass"]},
	{"question": "What stone evolves a Floette?","answers":["Shiny Stone","Shiny"]},
	{"question": "What does HM stand for?","answers":["Hidden Machine"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon that can evolve has the highest base stat total?","answers":["Porygon2","Porygon 2"]},
	{"question": "How many HMs were in Generation 1?","answers":["5","five","05"]},
	{"question": "In what Generation did Flash become a TM?","answers":["4","IV","four"]},
	{"question": "What is the first badge of the Kanto Region?","answers":["Boulder Badge","Boulder"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokémon with the same base stat total as its pre-evolution?","answers":["Scizor"]},
	{"question": "What is the heaviest Pokémon?","answers":["Cosmoem","Celesteela"]},
	{"question": "What is the biggest Pokémon by height?","answers":["Wailord"]},
	{"question": "What stat does the ability Rattled raise upon activation?","answers":["Speed","spe"]},
	{"question": "What is Blue's starter Pokémon in Yellow Version?","answers":["Eevee"]},
	{"question": "Most Professors in Pokémon games are named after what?","answers":["Trees","Tree"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon requires you to turn your DS upside down to evolve?","answers":["Inkay"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon evolves only in the rain?","answers":["Sliggoo"]},
	{"question": "What item do you need to find Shaymin in Generation IV?","answers":["Oak's Letter","oaks letter","oak letter"]},
	{"question": "Where can Mewtwo be found in Pokémon Red and Blue?","answers":["Cerulean Cave"]},
	{"question": "What item summons Arceus?","answers":["Azure Flute"]},
	{"question": "How many spoons does Mega-Alakazam have?","answers":["5","five"]},
	{"question": "What Generation first introduced shiny Pokémon?","answers":["2","II","two"]},
	{"question": "Confusion damage is based off of what stat?","answers":["Attack Stat","Attack","Atk stat","Atk"]},
	{"question": "How much HP does Leftovers cure every turn?","answers":["1/16","sixteenth","6.25%","one sixteenth"]},
	{"question": "What is the slowest move in the game?","answers":["Trick Room"]},
	{"question": "What is a special attack move that also makes contact?","answers":["Draining Kiss","Grass knot","Infestation","Petal dance","Trump card","Wring out"]},
	{"question": "What move has the highest base power?","answers":["Explosion"]},
	{"question": "How much do moves that hit multiple targets have their damage reduced by?","answers":["25%","1/4","Quarter","fourth"]},
	{"question": "What move has the highest chance to Freeze the target?","answers":["Secret Power"]},
	{"question": "What was Blizzard's accuracy in Generation 1?","answers":["90%","ninety","90"]},
	{"question": "What Generation introduced the most new moves?","answers":["1","one","I"]},
	{"question": "What is the lowest Accuracy for any ghost move?","answers":["100%","100"]},
	{"question": "What type besides Normal was immune to Ghost in Generation 1?","answers":["Psychic"]},
	{"question": "What is Super Effective against Poison besides Psychic and Ground in Generation 1?","answers":["Bug"]},
	{"question": "What type of Pokémon can always escape from trapping moves and abilities?","answers":["Ghost"]},
	{"question": "What determines whether you successfully run away from a battle?","answers":["Speed Stat","Speed","Spe"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon can evolve twice without leveling up?","answers":["Porygon"]},
	{"question": "What type has the most amount of moves?","answers":["Normal"]},
	{"question": "What was the first Pokémon created?","answers":["Rhydon"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon can learn every TM and HM?","answers":["Mew"]},
	{"question": "What is Mewtwo's birthday?","answers":["February 6th","February 6","Feb 6th","Feb 6","2/6"]},
	{"question": "What day can Lapras be found in Union Cave (Generation II)?","answers":["Friday"]},
	{"question": "How many turns do weather effects last unboosted?","answers":["5","five"]},
	{"question": "Can you name one of Meloetta's forms?","answers":["Pirouette","Aria"]},
	{"question": "What is the signature move of the Swords of Justice?","answers":["Sacred Sword"]},
	{"question": "What move transforms Keldeo into Resolute Form?","answers":["Secret Sword"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokémon from Generation 6 that can Mega evolve?","answers":["Diancie"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon is called the 'Legendary Pokémon'?","answers":["Arcanine"]},
	{"question": "How much does a Choice Scarf increase your Speed by?","answers":["x1.5","50%","half","fifty","1.5","150%"]},
	{"question": "Was the Ghost type Special or Physical prior to Generation 4?","answers":["Physical"]},
	{"question": "Besides Fairy, what type can Hidden Power not become?","answers":["Normal"]},
	{"question": "What type has the fewest physical moves?","answers":["Fairy"]},
	{"question": "What type has the fewest damage-dealing moves?","answers":["Fairy"]},
	{"question": "What type has the fewest non-damaging moves?","answers":["Dragon"]},
	{"question": "What is the most commonly gained type through Mega evolving?","answers":["Dragon"]},
	{"question": "Who is the fastest non-legendary Pokémon?","answers":["Ninjask"]},
	{"question": "What is the only type Greninja cannot become?","answers":["Fairy"]},
	{"question": "What non-legendary Pokémon has the highest base attack?","answers":["Mega Heracross"]},
	{"question": "What is the only type Grass has not been paired with?","answers":["Fire"]},
	{"question": "Parental Bond's second hit is what percent of the first hit's damage?","answers":["25%","quarter","1/4","fourth"]},
	{"question": "What ability specifically protects against being frozen?","answers":["Magma Armor"]},
	{"question": "Name a Pokémon that has the ability Levitate and another ability?","answers":["Bronzong","Bronzor","duskull","giratina"]},
	{"question": "Can you name a Pokémon in the Tao Trio?","answers":["Reshiram","Zekrom","Kyurem"]},
	{"question": "Name a Ground move that can hit a Flying type Pokémon?","answers":["Sand Attack","Thousand Arrows"]},
	{"question": "What is the last Pokémon in alphabetical order?","answers":["Zygarde"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokémon to have more than one category?","answers":["Hoopa"]},
	{"question": "What stat does Calcium increase?","answers":["Special Attack","special atk","Spa","Sp atk","Spatk"]},
	{"question": "How many EV's does a Iron, Zinc or Protein increase a stat by?","answers":["10","ten"]},
	{"question": "Which Pokémon is the only Semi-Pseudo Legendary from Kalos?","answers":["Noivern"]},
	{"question": "What type was added to Alolan Raichu?","answers":["Psychic"]},
	{"question": "Which Pokémon was originally intended to be the mascot (which is now Pikachu)?","answers":["Clefairy"]},
	{"question": "Which Pokémon is the only Ground type Psuedo-Legendary?","answers":["Garchomp"]},
	{"question": "Which Psuedo-Legendary has more than one immunity?","answers":["Hydreigon"]},
	{"question": "Which Psuedo-Legendary has the highest Special Defense stat?","answers":["Goodra"]},
	{"question": "Which Shadow Pokémon was owned by Evice (final boss) in Pokémon Colosseum?","answers":["Tyranitar"]},
	{"question": "Which Psuedo-Legendary's pre-evolution changes its type upon evolution to the final stage?","answers":["Dragonite","Tyranitar"]},
	{"question": "What is the most common typing across all fossil pokémon?","answers":["Rock"]},
	{"question": "Z Bug move is called what?","answers":["Savage Spin-Out","savage spinout","savage spin out"]},
	{"question": "Z Ice move is called what?","answers":["Subzero Slammer"]},
	{"question": "Pikashunium Z gives Pikachu what Z move?","answers":["10,000,000 Volt Thunderbolt","10000000 volt thunderbolt","10 million volt thunderbolt","10MV thunderbolt"]},
	{"question": "Guardian of Alola requires what item to use?","answers":["Tapunium Z"]},
	{"question": "Which Bug type Pokémon gains an additional typing upon Mega evolution?","answers":["Pinsir"]},
	{"question": "Snorlium Z upgrades which move?","answers":["Giga Impact"]},
	{"question": "Z weather moves raise what stat?","answers":["Speed","Spe"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokémon exclusive Z-move that is a status move?","answers":["Extreme Evoboost"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon is codenamed UB-02 Beauty?","answers":["Pheromosa"]},
	{"question": "The individual base stats of all the Ultra Beasts are what?","answers":["Prime Numbers","Prime","Primes"]},
	{"question": "What is the only GameCube game to fall under Generation II?","answers":["Super Smash Bros. Melee","Super smash bros melee","Melee"]},
	{"question": "What is the first float in the Super Smash Bros. Melee stage Poké Floats?","answers":["Squirtle"]},
	{"question": "Which starter from Generation II cannot be found in a Pokéball in Super Smash Bros. Melee?","answers":["Totodile"]},
	{"question": "International Police agent Anabel can be battled where in Pokémon Emerald?","answers":["Battle Tower"]},
	{"question": "Which game can you catch the most legendaries in?","answers":["Omega Ruby and Alpha Sapphire","Omega Ruby","alpha sapphire","Alpha sapphire and omega ruby"]},
	{"question": "Who runs and maintains the Pokémon Bank?","answers":["Brigette"]},
	{"question": "The Substitute doll was orignally based off of which Pokémon?","answers":["Rhydon"]},
	{"question": "The MissingNo. glitch in Red and Blue duplicates which item in your bag?","answers":["6th","6","sixth","Six"]},
	{"question": "What NPC Trainer has used the most unique Pokémon species in the series?","answers":["N"]},
	{"question": "What NPC is noted as speaking 'very fast', and has his text speed always set to fast?","answers":["N"]},
	{"question": "Which Pokémon game(s) have multiple difficulty levels?","answers":["Black and White 2","White and black 2","Black 2 and white 2","black 2","white 2","BW2","black white 2","white black 2"]},
	{"question": "Beast Balls have a catch rate multiplier of what when not used on an Ultra Beast?","answers":["x0.1","0.1","0.1x","10%","1/10"]},
	{"question": "Which Pokémon joined Lucario as the second Steel and Fighting type?","answers":["Cobalion"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Ice move with negative priority?","answers":["Avalanche"]},
	{"question": "To do the MissingNo. glitch in Gen 1, who must you talk to first?","answers":["Old Man","Oldman"]},
	{"question": "How many Unown forms are there?","answers":["28"]},
	{"question": "What is Charjabug's ability?","answers":["Battery"]},
	{"question": "What does TCG stand for?","answers":["Trading Card Game"]},
	{"question": "What Generation introduced Hidden Abilities?","answers":["V","5","five","black and white"]},
	{"question": "What ability increases Special Attack by x1.5 when burned?","answers":["Flare Boost"]},
	{"question": "What is the most common ability that is exclusively a hidden ability?","answers":["Rattled"]},
	{"question": "What ability is a copy of Filter, but is unaffected by Mold Breaker?","answers":["Prism Armor","prism armour"]},
	{"question": "RKS System will change your type if you are holding a what?","answers":["Memory","memory drive","memory disc"]},
	{"question": "Besides Super Luck what ability increases your critical hit ratio?","answers":["Merciless"]},
	{"question": "EP038 of the Pokémon anime was broadcasted once, then subsequently banned for reportedly causing what?","answers":["Epileptic Seizures","Seizures"]},
	{"question": "What unreleased Pokémon was first featured in Pokémon: The First Movie - Mewtwo Strikes Back?","answers":["Donphan"]},
	{"question": "What is the only pseudo-legendary Ash has owned?","answers":["Goodra"]},
	{"question": "The Marsh Badge is awarded by which Gym Leader?","answers":["Sabrina"]},
	{"question": "What is the only game where Lance doesnt use a Dragonite?","answers":["Pokemon Stadium","Poke Stadium","Stadium"]},
	{"question": "Besides Ditto what other pokémon is capable of breeding, but cannot be obtained through breeding?","answers":["Manaphy"]},
	{"question": "What suprising Pokémon can Skitty infamously breed with?","answers":["Wailord"]},
	{"question": "What move can be used outside of battle to heal your Pokémon?","answers":["Soft-Boiled","Soft boiled","Softboiled","Milk drink","milkdrink"]},
	{"question": "How many eyes do the Regi's have?","answers":["7","Seven"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokémon that learns Light of Ruin?","answers":["Eternal Flower Floette","eternal floette"]},
	{"question": "Pokémon Generations featured a protagonist from every generation except VII and what?","answers":["IV","4","four"]},
	{"question": "What type has been a gym or trial captain type in every generation?","answers":["Electric"]},
	{"question": "What Ground type Pokémon does Blue have as the champion in Generation I?","answers":["Rhydon"]},
	{"question": "The following Pokémon can be found in which city: Voltorb, Omanyte, Kangaskhan, Lapras?","answers":["Fuchsia City","Fuchsia"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokémon whose branched evolutions both evolve further?","answers":["Wurmple"]},
	{"question": "A glitch in Generation 1 allowed Pikachu or Eevee (Jolteon) to evolve after leveling up without an evolutionary stone, if what Pokémon finished the battle?","answers":["Growlithe"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon is known as the Trio Master of the Legendary Birds?","answers":["Lugia"]},
	{"question": "To unlock the Regi's caves you must have who in the front of your party?","answers":["Relicanth"]},
	{"question": "What is the base power of Explosion in generation 2-4 during damage calculation?","answers":["500"]},
	{"question": "Whose Pokémon storage system (PC) are you using in Generation 3?","answers":["Lanette","Lanettes","Lanette's"]},
	{"question": "How many boxes did you have in your PC in Generation 3?","answers":["14","fourteen"]},
	{"question": "What is the only HM with a unique type?","answers":["Rock Smash"]},
	{"question": "Generation IV introduced Defog and what other HM?","answers":["Rock Climb"]},
	{"question": "Who is the only Pokémon that is a Fighting and Ice type?","answers":["Crabominable"]},
	{"question": "Which Pokémon had the highest base Attack stat in Generation 1 and 2 (there are two, name one)?","answers":["Dragonite","Tyranitar"]},
	{"question": "Who is the tallest Steel Pokémon?","answers":["Steelix"]},
	{"question": "Eevee, Alomomola, and Girafarig are all what?","answers":["Palindromes","palindrome"]},
	{"question": "What is the only game to not require Surf (or Lapras/Sharpedo) in order to reach the Elite Four?","answers":["Black and White","White and black","black white","white black","white","black","black & white","white & black"]},
	{"question": "Kyogre, Sharpedo and what other Pokémon have unique surfing sprites in Omega Ruby and Alpha Sapphire?","answers":["Wailmer"]},
	{"question": "Which Generation 2 Pokémon has the lowest base Speed stat?","answers":["Shuckle"]},
	{"question": "Name one of the only two damaging moves whose animation plays out even if it has no effect or misses?","answers":["Explosion","Self-Destruct","self destruct","selfdestruct"]},
	{"question": "Which Generation 4 Pokémon has the lowest base Speed stat?","answers":["Munchlax"]},
	{"question": "Yo! Champ in the ______!?","answers":["Making"]},
	{"question": "Darmanitan gains what type in Zen Mode?","answers":["Psychic"]},
	{"question": "Shelmet will only evolve if traded for a what?","answers":["Karrablast"]},
	{"question": "Which Generation 7 Pokémon has the lowest base Speed stat?","answers":["Pyukumuku"]},
	{"question": "Which Baby Pokémon has the highest base stats total?","answers":["Munchlax"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon is a boss in Subspace Emissary?","answers":["Rayquaza"]},
	{"question": "Sawsbuck's forms are based off of what?","answers":["Seasons","season","the season","the seasons"]},
	{"question": "What item protects aginst effects caused by using a contact move on a target?","answers":["Protective Pads","protective pad"]},
	{"question": "What Generation II item boosts Attack by 2 stages then confuses the holder?","answers":["Berserk Gene"]},
	{"question": "What item boosts binding move's damage?","answers":["Binding Band"]},
	{"question": "What virus can Pokémon catch?","answers":["Pokerus"]},
	{"question": "What item boosts binding move's turn length?","answers":["Grip Claw","gripclaw"]},
	{"question": "What Egg Group does Ditto belong to?","answers":["Ditto Egg Group","ditto","ditto group"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Egg Group to contain a Pokémon of every type?","answers":["Undiscovered Egg Group","Undiscovered","undiscovered group"]},
	{"question": "What was the first pokémon to have gender differences?","answers":["Nidoran"]},
	{"question": "S.S. Aqua goes from Olivine City to where?","answers":["Vermilion City","Vermilion"]},
	{"question": "What is the ferry called in Hoenn?","answers":["S.S. Tidal","ss tidal"]},
	{"question": "What company makes the core-series Pokémon games?","answers":["GAME FREAK inc.","gamefreak inc.","gamefreak inc","game freak inc","gamefreak","game freak"]},
	{"question": "What item is used to summon Dialga?","answers":["Adamant Orb"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokémon to lose the ability to breed upon evolving?","answers":["Nidoran Female","female nidoran","f Nidoran","nidoran f","girl nidoran","nidoran girl"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon is the final ballon in Secret Super Training in Pokémon X or Y?","answers":["Mega Aggron","Mega Tyranitar","Mega-Aggron","Mega-Tyranitar"]},
	{"question": "What Steel move does not check Accuracy, excluding Z-moves?","answers":["Smart Strike"]},
	{"question": "What is Jirachi's Signature Move?","answers":["Doom Desire"]},
	{"question": "What Pokémon has the most unique TCG cards?","answers":["Unown"]},
	{"question": "What rare location appears randomly in Ruby/Sapphire/Emerald?","answers":["Mirage Island"]},
	{"question": "Where is the only place to find a Liechi Berry in Hoenn?","answers":["Mirage Island"]},
	{"question": "In Ruby/Sapphire/Emerald Pokéblock feeders in the Safari Zone attract Pokémon based on their what?","answers":["Nature"]},
	{"question": "What is the only Baby Pokémon with a branched evolution?","answers":["Tyrogue"]},
	{"question": "Which one of the following is NOT defined as a baby pokémon: Budew, Riolu, Tyrogue, Chingling, Eevee, Togepi?","answers":["Eevee"]},
	{"question": "Which Pokémon has the highest base HP of all Fire-type Pokémon?","answers":["Entei"]},
	{"question": "It's found crawling on beaches and seafloors. The coral that grows on Corsolas head is as good as a five-star banquet to this Pokémon. What pokémon is this?","answers":["Mareanie"]},
	{"question": "Roark's father is the Gym leader of what city?","answers":["Canalave city","canalave"]},
	{"question": "How many Rock-type Gym leaders are there in total (including all generations)?","answers":["4","four"]},
	{"question": "What is Blaine's strongest Pokémon in Red/Blue/Yellow?","answers":["Arcanine"]}
]